Lets get itstraight; Berk
Letsgetitstraight; Berk
Lets get it straight; Berk
Lets getit straights Berk
Lets getitstraight, Berk.
~Serous about what?
Areyou serious?
Serious about what?
Are you serious?
likeanapkin?
mean;areyou going to use me
mean,areyou going to use me
Imean; areyou going to use me
[ikeanapkin?
mean; areyou going t0 use me
mean;areyou going t0 use me
areyou going to use me
mean;areyou going to use me
like a
1 mean, are you going to use me
about that napkin thing
Actually , I've always wondered
Actually , l've always wondered
aboutthat napkin thing .
Actually; [ve always wondered
aboutthat napkin thing.
Actually; [Fvealways wondered
about that napkin thing:
Actually , l've always wondered
Whynapkin? Why not socks?
Why napkin?
aswell_
Weuseandthrow them away
as well_
We use and throw them away